Automakers and tech companies are working hard to offer the first true self -driving
car, but 75 of say they wouldn't feel safe in such a vehicle.
car, but 75 of drivers say they wouldn't feel safe in such a vehicle.
Still, of would like to get some kind of self -driving feature,
such as automatic braking or self -parking, the next time they buy a new car.
Still, get -driving -parking, car.
Still, 60 of drivers would like to get some kind of self -driving feature, such as
automatic braking or self -parking, the next time they buy a new car.
Still, 60 of drivers would like to get some kind of self -driving feature,
such as automatic braking or self -parking, the next time they buy a new car.
The Attitudes are published in a new AAA survey of 1,800 drivers.
Advocates of self -driving cars argue they would be safer than in cars driven by
humans because they wouldn't get distracted or drive when tired.
But those surveyed by AAA say they trust their own driving skills.
Many feel the technology is too new and unproven.
But those surveyed by AAA say